famouspoetsandpoems.com 2016-12-03

# Privacy Policy - Famous Poets and Poems

The FamousPoetsAndPoems.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [FamousPoetsAndPoems.com](http://www.famouspoetsandpoems.com/)

**Advertisers**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Recommending a Poems**  
When you recommend a poems to a friend from our site, we ask for both your email address and your friend's. We not share this information with third parties and we do not collect or use e-mail addresses of the senders or the recipients for any purposes. 

**IP Addresses**  
We collect and analyze traffic on our web site by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. An IP address is a unique number assigned to your computer when you are browsing the internet. We log this information so that we can monitor overall traffic trends as well as the number of visitors visiting the web site. This information is used SOLELY to improve the quality of our web site. 

**Cookies**  
We use a technology nicknamed "cookies" on our web site. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your rowser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to make your visit to our web site easier. Cookies also allow us to count the number of unique and return visitors who use our site. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. 

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [Contact Us](http://www.famouspoetsandpoems.com/contact_us.html)
